[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Baton Rouge is the capital of what US state?", "correct_answer": "Louisiana", "incorrect_answers": ["New Hampshire", "Maine", "North Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what approximate speed does the Earth orbit around the Sun?", "correct_answer": "108 000 km/h (67 108.1 mph)", "incorrect_answers": ["18 000 km/h (11 184.7 mph)", "10 000 km/h (6 213.7 mph)", "1000 km/h (621.4 mph)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Billy Ray is begging for money on the street in the movie Trading Places, he has a sign around his neck.  What does the sign say?", "correct_answer": "A grateful war veteran thanks you. Merry Christmas", "incorrect_answers": ["I will work for food", "I am not going to lie. I want money for a beer", "I am down on my luck, how bout forking over a buck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The nickname of this U.S. state is The Equality State. Its motto is Equal Right.", "correct_answer": "Wyoming", "incorrect_answers": ["Colorado", "Maryland", "Vermont"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the favorite victim of The Hook according to the popular urban legend?", "correct_answer": "A young couple", "incorrect_answers": ["A drunkard", "An old woman", "A naughty child"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the highest rated science-fiction movie on the AFI Top 100 list?", "correct_answer": "Star Wars (1977)", "incorrect_answers": ["Close Encounters of the Third Kind", "E.T. The Extra-Terrestrial", "2001: A Space Odyssey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Matrix, Bound and Speed Racer are directed by two brothers who are also motion picture writers and producers. What is their last name?", "correct_answer": "Wachowski", "incorrect_answers": ["Coen", "Grant", "Parks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress plays Vanessa Loring, the woman who wants to adopt Junos child in the movie Juno. She acted in Felicity with first husband Scott Foley but has a child with second husband, Ben Affleck.", "correct_answer": "Jennifer Garner", "incorrect_answers": ["Dana Clark", "Kerri Russell", "Jennifer Anniston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the difference between the male and the female Galah, a cockatoo bird native to Australia?", "correct_answer": "Males and females have different eye colour.", "incorrect_answers": ["There is no difference between them.", "Galah males are crested.", "Galah females have shorter tails."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do viruses reproduce?", "correct_answer": "By forcing other cells to produce copies of them", "incorrect_answers": ["By transforming other cells into viruses", "By cell division", "By maitng"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This duo had a critical success in 2002\u2019s Unfaithful. In 2008 they sparkle in \u201cNights in Rodanthe.", "correct_answer": "Diane Lane and Richard Gere", "incorrect_answers": ["Julia Roberts and Richard Gere", "Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt", "Angelina Jolie and Clive Owens"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The original name of which city is translated as The Great City of Angels\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Bangkok", "incorrect_answers": ["Vadodara", "Los Angeles", "Bogot\u00e1"]}]